Well, let's begin.
We have 25 people in our chat.
Hey, hi everyone.
Means,
Today,
Well, this is my first experience too.
holding a webinar, so I ask
I don't judge too harshly, but I was prepared and wanted to
make sure that today's meeting
gave, well, real benefit and so that tomorrow
it was possible to start using it
modern tools. And I personally
I'm using these tools now
just every day. And in fact, all of mine
the work was reduced to one window in which
I am here. This is a raft.
And today, imagine work without
I, for example, no longer have this instrument
Can. That is, I don’t understand, eh, what
Why else can you do this on a computer?
if you do not use this tool.
Well, that's probably what we're talking about
let's talk.
And whoever is there, whoever is comfortable, turn it on.
cameras. It's always nicer to see faces
reactions. And if there are any questions, uh,
Write in chat. I will either be on them as far as possible
answer, or we will just follow them in the end,
Let's go through them all. Well, in general, everything is as it is
usually. I think everyone has already said this a million times
passed. I won't repeat myself here. A
Let's structure the presentation as follows.
I'll give you some general introduction first, and then the closer I get
by the end, the more demonstration there will be
screens and stories about what it is, why
This is how it works.
Well, here's a little news. Literally there
Many people probably saw Friday.
The American company spent 500 million
dollars per claude. So if you have
I have a subscription and there is an extra 500 on my account.
million dollars, better put it
limitation to avoid getting into such a situation
situation. And the company KemG, global
consulting company concluded
strategic partnership with anthropic.
276,000 employees are connected to the mode
constant work through Claude and their
services. And two more companies.
They probably mean nothing to me or to you either.
they will say. These are some kind of global ones
American consulting companies. IN
one more 470,000 employees and one more
for 110,000 employees. are crossing over
The company is entirely committed to working with Claude.
A
today, probably, if you look at a
equal players, and I would highlight four of them
the main ones, yes, the AIs themselves, there are dozens of them,
if not hundreds, but those that help
every day at work for each of us, this
the well-known GPT chat, and this is a samclod,
eh, Perplexity is also like that
A worthwhile experience in its own right. Open Cloud is
a thing that is exactly about what she
say she will do everything herself. But we have it
We won't touch on it at all today, because
what will she do so that you will then
you will be left without data and will simply give it away
put everything out on the Internet
it is possible, including data, there are their own maps and
everything else. This is such a big one
A geeky story, albeit a very powerful one.
And in dialogue I mean that everyone is like
At least I used GPT chat. I think,
Today there are no people who don't do this
passed.
It's everywhere, but we'll talk about it.
about
Claude
Perplexity. CLD and GPT, they are coming now
approximately, ah, nazdrya in nazdrya.
Claude puts a lot of emphasis on the side
corporate application and makes it very
many tools that allow
start working with it quickly and
implement into your business. Plexity
practically
the same. That is, if you put
tell yourself about these applications, you will see that they
even externally they are very similar. GPT has a little bit
This is different.
So, let's start with the basic definitions.
What are we going to talk about anyway?
Terminology,
tools with examples. And, well, I'll show you,
Yes, where to start today,
tomorrow and what to take to work.
as I said, huh
This meeting today is for those who
is, probably, first of all
leader. And the one who sees big
the volume of data and work around itself,
a large volume of analytics should
make decisions. And I will do it here
corrections to what I mean,
you have access to almost everything
data that you will be with
interact during your work.
And our task is, uh, to learn
set goals for yourself, learn to set them
tasks for employees, learn to communicate
With
with these systems, yes, in the same language.
And don't forget that everything we do
we will do everything that we will
discussing this, well, these systems don't carry
no responsibility, right?
The responsibility always lies with the one who
uses it. And this also applies to access
to data, use of data, and that
the responsibility you create for
surrounding people, using modern
tools.
A
so, well, it's the same here, I guess.
So, let's start with the analysis,
a little confusion aa
in terminology.
Again, I proceed from the fact that
not all IT specialists, and
I'll try, probably, yes, somehow
today we need to build a dialogue in such a way that
It would have been possible to add IT specialists later
connect, speak with them in the same language
language. And there is often confusion in IT
AI, yes, people want to be in companies
implement both, often confusing them,
which of these is what, which is for what
what is needed and how it all works. Eat
automation confusion, analytics,
the data seems to be needed, where is it
see how to get to them, how to get them
unload, how to synchronize them.
We'll just touch on this briefly. But what is needed?
understand? Well, all these terms are, by
essentially layers of the same thing.
Aishka can be used on your
desktop. You can use it with
have access to your desktop
to almost all of its corporate
instruments, to all of their own, and, there,
databases, data, systems, anything.
But in order to organize the work
systemic, in order to implement these
tools for the work of other employees,
in order to implement this into work,
your business processes, this is not the place to be
to do without that very automation, no
do without analytics. The most important thing is,
all this is done on the IT layer, namely
IT, IT specialists bring it all together
under one wing and allow
interact with all these tools
together.
And what is important today, thanks to,
the spread of vibe coding, thanks to
the fact that these technologies have become simple,
available, and a huge number of things appear
number of specialists. and, unfortunately,
pseudo-specialists who,
eh, well, they can collect anything there
very quickly and show you the finished ones
tools. This is indeed true. A
this, uh, technology allows today
I don't know, you should launch a mobile app there.
application, release a new website,
make a mini-apk or whatever,
set up any synchronization.
But the Devil is always in the details. Aa I'm exactly right
for the same reason, we always have, uh,
big arguments with my partner there. He
just that very IT guy, and he's on it
everyone is looking, uh, well, with
from another point of view, yes, it is not enough to create
system, it is important to ensure
low-level. Access control,
redundancy of the system itself,
backup of data with which
this system works, provide a circuit,
which you have facing outwards, ensure
safety loop between employees.
Yes, you work with both finance and
personal data, and with anything. U
you have technical support chats there,
Consulting, sales, anything.
It's important, ah, to keep it under control. AND
the products that are being created today, they
must be in the same contour
and providing and answering to everyone
the requirements of this security, including
including versioning of the product itself.
Aishka
good for
creating some kind of MVP product there. You
You can quickly try it out and release it.
and try to sell it, and you have it
they will buy it, and you can build on it. There
the unicorn is already being designed,
and there are such examples in the world.
But if this application is not built, and
according to all the canons of programming, no
support versioning, management
and so on, then with the next one
update your sold solution
just flies into the trash because it
stops working properly. And Ishka is not
remembers and doesn't know what you have there
app, right? She can make mistakes and
she will make mistakes. And it is important to build
This work is based on IT.
So whatever you do now,
If you didn't look in Aishka's direction, what
she is so needed and she is good, and the first one,
who you need in the company is not
an IT specialist, or an IT specialist who can do this
organize everything properly.
What we are, uh, discussing now, uh, well,
I guess you could say that it's already
obsolete because
all the listed systems are developing
in eight-step steps. But I work
inside the claude, I have it all the time
It's updated, I get about a day there
five to seven updates. And about once a
in a month and a half all the giants are like there
Anthropic, Open A are releasing an update,
which simply turns you upside down
head all systems. It becomes
so much more powerful, so much more precise,
faster and more developed in every sense,
what we did there for 3 months
back, now it's done much faster,
much more effective.
Plus,
and we can't forget about, uh, that development,
which is happening now, and around us. This
concerns robotics.
A,
that is, all these possibilities
of a redeeming intellect, they certainly
are applied there, right? And this is the part,
which will also gradually replace
some functions and work functions, in
including interface changes. A
Everything we do today, we try
attract
data to, well, to the human species, to to
the format we are all accustomed to
work, yes. We love to look at
graphs, dashboards, some
signs,
press buttons. But
what's important is that today, uh, there are big ones
companies
they are already starting to develop and implement
products with a completely different
interface, yes, the same one there
phone, I'm there, well, we all through
for a while it won't matter what you have
We have an application there and how is it?
works. They are already starting to appear
applications. devices that work
just like voice assistants there,
Yes, this is the size of the case from
headphones, a device that is simple
listens, answers, it's under the hood itself
It crawls around, collects the necessary data, it does it itself
understands what you need and builds it,
for example, there is the same analytics and
make yourself some kind of dashboard, and before
which you need to reach, yes, to open
some page to look at
this dashboard.
Soon we will just be
to address, let's say: "Ah, show me
a dashboard of what I have there now
is happening, there are the main indicators." And
This system will collect from yours on Lita
numbers, from your dashboard data
there is any color, any shape for any
the device, or it will simply dictate it to you
the result you want to hear and
will do it more accurately and better than you even
formulate what you want now
see on this dashboard.
Therefore, of course, it is necessary to do this
turn on. And I'm here
I would like to emphasize once again that it is precisely
at the IT level, we'll talk about that today
talk more, uh, because everything
systems, they work with the data,
which you have. Data is being collected
Outside of IT again. Aishka is like the top
layer that can with them
interact.
Ah, well, let's move on to the most important thing, I guess.
the main one. Ah, well, there is such an expression,
What
80% of the answer is contained in the question. Here it is
working with
AI systems, and everything is exactly like that
same. AND
I will speak now about your request.
banal things. You've probably seen them.
everything is somewhere in rice. and so on, right?
Here are these comparisons, request, there, do it
give me a presentation or make me one
presentation on such and such a topic for
such-and-such audience, for such-and-such period,
such and such a platform, you get
completely different things. And I'll tell you now
I'll demonstrate, well, an example of a request,
which, uh, here are most of the examples
there will be, uh, something from my personal life, yes,
how do I work with it there and what
I get the result from this. and what
the result this gives to the company, including
and in the value of the company.
And with Aishka,
when you start with her
to interact, you need to communicate with both
as with a person, no matter how trivial it may be
it sounded like there was an employee there who
I just came to your company. He
doesn't know anything about you or about
your company. He doesn't know how you are
set tasks, how you work with it.
AND
it will depend exactly on the input data
the result you will get.
Here
It's important, but not just to formulate
the task, but supply it with the data,
which should be at the input of the solution
this task, but also try harder
maintain that same focus a-a for
obtaining the desired result. If you are for
dump the entire volume there once
documentation, that's all about my
company, go figure it out, no one
will figure it out. We ourselves, yes, how is it
managers, we cannot always understand and
we can't always figure out what's going on there
your papers, documents, and so on. A
Exactly the same thing is happening here. So,
I'll switch now
screen. Wait a second.
So, huh,
Can I ask you to put it, uh, somehow?
react, put pluses, who
Is anyone familiar with the fruit at all? Who is with it?
works and who works with the fetus.
Give me one plus. I tried it, I saw it. Uh
There are two plus signs working, including with
Claude Cowork, because that's the main
the tool we'll be talking about today
speak.
Yes.
Artem, Lyudmila.
Yes. It didn't work with the code. This
next level. Open cloud. Great.
A
so, uh, here
This is what the window looks like.
Uh,
right now, just a second.
This is what Claude's window looks like. Basic
desktop, which consists of three
parts. Hey, this is the chat tab everyone knows.
GPT chat.
Exactly the same, yes, individual
some individual requests. A
the only difference here is
you can enable the memory of these chats or
Turn off the memory of these chats. And here you are,
eh, you analyze, you ask some questions
standard questions, you get answers to them
answers. Well, implying that it is
some kind of one-time story, yes, you came
ask here, inquire and so on
further. What we are going to talk about is
This product is called Svor, which
implies use, work in
within the framework of projects. So here we are
we're starting a separate project for ourselves, which
how the entity will unite everything in itself
the data you work with,
documents that you will be uploading to
project and which Claude will give you
create as a result of one's own
activities in this project. And there too
you can connect a huge number of
external sources. We're talking about that too.
let's talk. Well, here we are now
Let's open it, just a second, I'll open it
An example of a query that I made for a
developments
Miniapa mobile application.
Just one second. What's important is not
only, but to formulate it correctly
task, but also one of the main functions, and
systems, she knows how to formulate, she
knows how to, uh, debate and bring things to a head
dialogue, and she can make speeches. If you
connect everything together, these
moments in your work, then you will
get a good result. Here it is
For example, we have help here now.
I need to prepare and develop me tt. I
I'm describing it here, but based on my own
experience is all I want to get. But
Next, I'll add the important things here.
Here. That is, the top part, I just
I'm giving you the context of what I'd like
get it, right? And then I add more
First, question me thoroughly, study me
practices available on Reddit and on
GitHub, explore what's out there
Russian market in this industry, then
formation of the final technical specifications and so on
further. Now we have reached the point
five. It was there that he switched to others
tasks, but here is the answer I get
from this system. That is, he first
Yes, yes, yes, I understood everything. Okay, let's go.
Uh, that's how he got such and such information there.
He throws in a lot of things, but then he
starts preparing a list for me here
questions for me. I ask myself these questions
when setting tasks, probably never
I wouldn't have asked. Aa agent is studying my
request, the agent starts to walk me through
interview with me. That is, this interview
How much will we have here now?
points? Ah, 44 points. He asks me
questions that make me
think about what I'm doing, why I'm doing it
I'm doing how it will work, how it is
there will be something arranged under the hood, I took it into account
I have the requirements of the federal law there.
152, for example, yes, what systems are we
we use. That is, uh,
This is the technical specifications for my Rains project,
already knows a lot about R, but I
I'm getting him to start
ask additional questions. I
I answer him a few questions,
All. And after that he piles on me,
Now I'll show him and he'll give me a hard time
next half of questions. This one here
dialogue, it can last quite a long time
long, huh? That means you can spend
there really, I don't know, it takes 2 hours
communication because it is communication
It means not only there, but everything
like do it yourself. You order from him
the product you will use,
that your team will use
and which will be used by your
clients. This is a product that will fit in
your company's legacy that will enhance
the value of your company. And here it is important,
A,
Well, prepare well and work
It's right to delve into these answers. Not,
not just [ __ ] off, yes. Here. Here's what happens next
He threw another 60 answers at me. Oh, 60
there are 69 questions, how many more are there?
and so on. That is, here, uh, here is this
communication, this long sheet -
This is my work with him. As a result, he
it gives me
now, where is he there,
a second. He himself lost himself in his fruit.
I won't look for it now. All in all,
It outputs A in the format I need, AAA.
text. Oh, sorry, I pulled it out for myself.
separately for work on the desktop. He
pulls it out for me,
he creates a document for me, further, which
I'll have to review it and make some corrections.
feed this document back to him. What
It's interesting, in the process of this work, and
he prepared a solution for me and
at the end, and he said that this is it
solution, there is one of the functions I have,
for example, yes, it was in the project, it's protection
projects. to interact with our
dealer partners. And at our market
This is such a common thing. Protection
projects, it is not always and not for everyone
works well.
Together with him we described this
such a product, such a solution that
Claude wrote to me at the end. It's like
The solution is worthy of a good patent. such:
"Okay, let's study the patent now.
patent history and see if there is any
something similar."
He does resarch, he, uh, collects
information and does not find it. That is, what I am
I'll take this next step? I'll tell him now:
"Now prepare me a patent application and
send it to my patent attorney,
to send another one for registration
additional document." That is, here
there behind
there are 2-3 hours, I don’t know, I don’t remember anymore,
How long did it take and I get
the most detailed technical specifications that were given for work.
And this is the technical specifications
I will show examples further that this is not
just words, yes, that's the TZ here we are
We did it, it's such a cool picture
It worked out and they put it on the table. I
Now I'll show you more examples of how this
tez works and the products we already have
We did it according to the same scheme. That is, in
as a result of three hours of work there I
I receive a great technical specification for a new product,
which will be created with the help of Claude, and
At the same time, I will also send the patent
I will apply and receive a patent for the system
order management and project protection.
So at this moment I'm just creating
additional value to the company.
And, as I said,
Aishka is strong in formulating problems, in
research and in,
Well, in a joint venture.
A,
ok, sorry, I jumped ahead.
When you form
task to the fetus,
don't forget to point him out, uh, there,
ask him to do extra
work. That is, if you don’t understand
in some topic, and we still don’t
We're figuring it out, yes, we can't do everything
understand everything, therefore, when describing
task if it is directed to popular
resources that are very good there
indexed, which are simply
knowledge base for these systems, the same
GitHub, Redit and many others. A
plus there are still, uh, sources,
which connect to the cloud as
source of knowledge.
he will give you the most expert advice
answer. And he will conduct an analysis. He will conduct
competitor analysis, he will conduct an analysis
other solutions and will tell you how to do it
better.
What is very important is, of course, not in any way
in this case, do not immediately agree with what
he answers you. That is
responsibility, as I said, is always
it lies with the one who makes this decision
work both in your interests and for
obtaining a quality product
check, proofread and
as if to confirm that yes, everything is understood
That's right and we can work with it.
So, further.
The quality of the answer is equal to the quality of the question.
And here
When working with AE projects, you give Claude
a large amount of information. That is,
Claude is here, I'll take a look now, I think,
This will be our next slide. And at
Claude has a folder in which it is stored
everything you will interact with.
That is, the first thing in order to get
a quality answer, you must explain
to him, who are you, why are you, what are you doing,
What is your goal? This work, however it may seem
It's strange, it's best to do the same thing
with Claude. That is, from a clean establishment
project. We'll get to that too. And you?
you explain to him on your fingers, yes, what the
the project, what it is about and what it is for, and after
you start to have this same conversation with him
the discussion itself. Yes, I need to collect
such and such data, I want to describe the project
there for this and that. I have
such and such a set of aa services there,
instruments with which I
I interact. I have it stored there
so-and-so, so-and-so, so-and-so. build me something like this
work cycle, so that the result
as a result of this cycle, you, I,
Claude had full information about the project.
What is important here? Aa all AI systems
work with the window, the token window, the window
memory. Claude has this, uh, this window.
million tokens. This is very big
volume, but
if you just dump all the information on him,
exactly the same about the project as we do
They said, yes, about a new employee there.
it comes to you, you say: "This is it
everything you need to know about the company." He
will never know this in his life. He
will take only those parts that
are needed. Claude can take everything you have
they gave it to him. He has a big window.
opportunities. He will eat it all and then
will write to you: "I've run out of tokens,
and you will wait for a new session, because
that he won't figure out that you are from him
"You want." But you need to set goals
necessarily in the context of what you are talking about
do you want to work with him? If you now
He needs analytics, you give him analytics,
you give these numbers. If you need any
marketing research, you put
the task is precisely about these marketing
research.
As an example, right now, just a second, okay,
I'll show you an example later. So, is it good?
a request is to explain who is doing what, to give
context, and
after that you can get, uh, that
the result you expect
get.
Data is everything. And let's get back to
IT specialist.
The first thing you will need to do is
your company, is to build a system
working with data. Now for this
there are a large number
modern tools that
allow you to do this without resorting to
some kind of complex developments and so on
further. There are cloud databases now
data, there are simple databases that
unfold in your outline. This
wiki systems and much, much more. AND
all these products, they
allow us to systematize
data that Aishka will use in the future
will work. And we started with the fact that
today we are talking about what you
as a leader,
Well, you may not have access to everything there.
with this, yes, set up APIs there, receive
passwords, access to anything. But
to get started, you can start at
myself to work on the computer, and
to form these documents because
often, and many documents and many
knowledge, they are only there in
the founder's head. And, well, no one else
won't guess about them. This is a task
there as a leader, yes, or
the head of his department these
to systematize the data correctly,
lay it out correctly and put it as
the source of truth in one place, for example,
in Wiki or in the database with which in
AI will work in the future.
in the process of work, and, I interact with
AI, AI will create documents for you
on your desktop, oh, in yours
working folder of the project.
After some time these documents
there will be such a quantity about one and the same thing
same. And there, I don’t know, you do,
describe the company's strategy there or
not even a strategy, there, I don’t know, your
your mission, the company's mission. You
wrote 10 sheets of this mission there. IN
in the process of preparing this mission you have
A dozen drafts appeared there. Do you have
some intermediate aa appeared
pieces of text or anything.
While you are working on your project and
interaction with Aishka, she will do this
will eat everything and give you porridge.
Therefore, the task and the work are built
as follows. You are creating a task
there, within the framework of one session, you work,
did you get some good
document, we've already read it
We checked it ourselves, without AI,
said, "Yeah, okay, that's what I had.
in mind. Remember this." And this
you have the document as a source
truth. Well, for example, in yours
corporate wiki system. All
the rest of the drafts, you can save them
in yourself, you can put them somewhere
side, but with each new request
Your AI should go and get the source.
truth from there. If you want something
change, you will go and change in that
the system itself in the future. But if you
If you keep all this to yourself, then
with each new request you will receive
more and more porridge. Whatever
token window at Claude's or another
there was no system, it happened at some point
it will get clogged, and you will start having those same
hallucinations that irritate everyone.
Now Flood practically has them already
corrected from and got rid of
haevolutions, there are practically none of them
exists. Well, I didn't really succeed.
get them there. And I have developers
the same thing, well, that's not the case anymore
they see. But here, uh, the hygiene of this data,
She is very important. And without her
As is the input, so is the output.
A
Now let me show you more
screen.
Here is the formulation of the development task, uh,
technical specifications for the system, uh,
production planning system.
And the text is also quite large. This
final. There were several approaches
work in there in other chats, others
sessions.
Everything that is required is described here,
the system that needs to be made. Here
the results of this work, again, yes, to
returning to the value it gives, and
this work was done there again
in literally a few hours. And by
In fact, we got something like this
a large technical specification, which describes,
planning module control system
produced by RINS. Here is the fourth one
We wrote it on the sixteenth. Here
Described how it works and where it comes from. This is all
Claude writes, naturally. A,
I mean
By
by default, what I have here in
he already knows the systems in Raines' project
which we work. I had them before that
I taught before. He has the necessary
access to systems and much, much more
other. This is the technical specification that goes from me to mine
to the developer.
He spends several more hours there.
bringing this technical specification to the final stage.
And as a result
Here are the ready-made technical specifications using the code
this block
They give the job to Claude. Actually,
It took us a while to develop such a system
and eight working days, that is one and a half
weeks. And this is taking into account, of course,
developer's time.
And I'll show it there later in the future. Ah-ah,
We have already implemented the system after
8 days. And from the same code we
we get
we receive information about similar
developments. He counts the number
lines of code, it calculates those roles,
which are needed for development. A
the cost of this solution that we
They did it, it's about a 3.54 million fork
rub. and the period for such development of the procedure
there for 5 months.
We do it with one person in 8
working days, one and a half weeks. Second
solution
our wiki, with which we interact.
Right now, just a second,
another screen.
This is our corporate system.
management. Ah, getting back to the conversation.
about
data, where it should be stored, when
we are finally back on track
transition to AI and working with data, and,
Well, the first task that I have is
We got up, but where will we be?
store and how should it be stored? Well,
the solution is obvious, right? Wiki
have been there for decades, all of them
they use it. There are cloud wikis, there are
wikis that are installed in the circuit
companies, there are Wikis that
are installed on the desktop. Meaning
it doesn't change much. If the company
small or if all this data
are kept by you as a manager, you
You can collect this Wiki on your site
desktop and use it. If
you, uh, are building some kind of story
big,
and you want to continue this data
reuse,
then, well, of course, we need to raise Wiki
in its own company circuit. This is it again
We're getting back to IT. But we went
along a different path. We looked at everything
existing solutions. They are here again
same, cloud, there are paid ones, there are
free, but they all have them
some of their own limitations.
And in order to be normal
integrate this system in compliance
access rights, subject to the rights
with versioning, with a backup there
copying and everything else, and since
For us, it's not just a Wiki, it's a system,
which unites all knowledge in general
companies and including Big Data data
our products and production data
and there is synchronization and everything else.
It was decided that we are writing to Wikipedia.
on one's own. I don't care about this block at all
didn't touch. This is what my partner did.
programmer. A
this decision was written there around
the same time frame, one and a half to one week.
Wikis integrated from scratch, taking into account
all access rights, taking into account everyone there
versioning, taking into account our
products, taking into account our
business processes.
And while he was writing it, I, together with Claude,
Sorry, I have to go back and forth
switch between screens. I'm with Claude
was involved in filling this data.
What does it look like? We'll open it now.
some
sh impression.
I have a big ruler there.
product information.
And I fed him the file. Now, in my opinion,
This is a different chat. Well, it doesn't matter. I told him
I fed the file that was there before
somewhere around six months or a year ago, probably
I was sitting back and dictating at that moment
more GPT. GPT interviewed me on
my product. Here in the mode, you,
Probably everyone saw, he was getting lost, yes, when
GPT can be communicated with by voice. This is very
cool and comfortable. And you,
Well, you feel like a human being because
why are you sitting and talking?
in human language and explain that
you need it. A
GPT itself leads you into dialogue and further
They ask questions, right? But again, to him
I must say that you are picking on things there
until the last comma,
Get all the information out of me. Like this
I probably had an interview there too
It's about an hour and a half there. I sat with him,
communicated. After that I transcribed everything
it's in
file and fed
into this system.
Here, I probably have this
transcribation was the first.
I don't see. Okay, there are a lot of sessions. A
While my partner was creating the Wiki, I was
I was filling the Wiki format with a-a content
information on each product. What are they
differ in how they work. eh, what are you
their configurations, how they are connected to each other
interact, what can be done with what there
connect, and what can't be connected with what, and so on
further. That is, this data
right now, I still have them in my
in my computer and in the cloud. I am them
I use it as a data source. That is
when I say to Claude: "Now do it
I don't know, should I make a presentation or something?
I need analytics on such and such products or
Let's come up with a new idea." A
a new idea for a new product,
He fully understands my whole context.
Now I repeat, this is on my
computer, but next time it's already there
on Vika. We're just not on Vika yet
made the connection. I think that in
In the coming days it will be there too
made. And I clean all this up and
I'm connecting our Wiki as a single source
data for
Well, as a single source of truth for everything
products. And all our Wiki
becomes available accordingly to the whole
the team, the whole company. All who will be
work with Claude locally or in
further with the agents, they all have
a common knowledge base about everything appears
our products, about all our, ah, numbers,
data. And what is important again is that it is always
I will emphasize that it is very important to keep in mind
all the IT stuff in my head, because now
us, if we post everything on Wikipedia, then
later during construction a
systems, such as customer support,
some analytics, and external chats,
eh, an external person comes into the chat for
technical support,
and Claude GPT doesn't care what will be under there
under the hood, he might just dump everything on him
your data because he has
access to all your data, including
accounting, including personal data
employees and so on. That is, this one
automation and these accesses, they
are very important. You can do it now
It's fast, simple, and it flies, and that's what you need
to use. But we must not forget about
safety.
We're going back to We're going back to
presentation.
So, well, here I think I said, yes,
the more data, the, the more
context, the better. But context is needed
give in doses,
don't put in any extra stuff. text, text,
tables, and this is the best fuel for
your system. And I'll show you later too,
for example, how can you raise it now?
bases, uh, to the person who is with this
I have never communicated in my life and I don't
understands what a database is. AND
There are online solutions that are already available today
are used by many people, and they
as simple as possible, and yet they are all
already have the opportunity today
connecting these systems to
to your II products.
Pictures with some data inside.
files, I don't know, there are presentations, too
something, they read well. pictures,
if you, uh, are having a dialogue with Aishka on
some topic, you have as
there is, for example, only one source
picture, but don't feed it directly
there too, because Aishka will be
read this picture, it will do
reverse promng, how is this picture,
It is arranged that it is not written. She
he's just scoring himself again
context and then she will be uh
use this context inside there
answers that you will receive from her.
Therefore, it is a good option if the data
unclean, that's what we'll call them, yes, that's it
the picture is some kind of raster and that's all
the rest, go to a separate session,
you feed a picture here, you say like this
What's on it? Take the data from here and give it to me.
I'm in good shape. and then this one
You are already giving the result back to the context.
In general, well, it's like, very
small comment, but, uh, I'm trying
to convey that it is very important to keep this
work hygiene and not to pollute the context,
Yes, it's the same as jumping over there
from topic to topic when setting some
tasks.
And I think I've already said about this too.
And everything that you have been working on
inside
your aishka,
inside your project, conduct
check, separate the important things, what you
accepted what you read manually for
outside of Aishka. You said, "Yes, this one
The document is good. Take out the trash,
leave only what you have approved,
so that your next requests come from
this point, and not from that, not from some
previous thoughts. And no need for AI
refer, yes, as we sometimes do in dialogue
we try to remember something and start: "A
Do you remember, he said something there, no
She needs to know about this." She doesn't remember and
knows nothing. She's just using
it's like uh
crap up your brain. Nothing extra.
So, how does Ai think and what does she remember, and
Why is she sometimes stupid?
So what's the difference?
AII systems from some script
system or hard code? And if you are in
you give the program some input
data or table, and to some
script, you will get the output that
the result you expect to see.
If you ask the same question
Aishki, she will answer you now like this, and
in 5 minutes you will ask the same question
question, she will answer differently.
And it is a probabilistic model, it
is engaged, and,
Well, it's a generative model that
selects words and there meanings
depending on this with the vector of weights
and so on. That is, she
each time the answer will be plus or minus
Right. Well, same thing again
well, yes, ask 10 people there, ask
the same question. If this is a question
something understandable and anyone can do it
answer, you will get the same
result, correct answer. But everyone
will say it in his own words. Same here
the most. And this is important to take into account when
building automation within AI. We
We'll get to her too.
And when Aishka is built inside
some kind of automation,
into which you always have one entrance,
for example, data from your CRM, data from
your 1C, from anywhere, you have the exit
will be different. And just like that, straight to the forehead,
if it's, for example, a support chat,
Most likely, there are no questions. Let her
he will answer now this way, tomorrow that way, to everyone
will be in its own way, and she will be all the time
answer correctly, but a little
differently. A,
but if you have some numbers there, no
I know, there are accounting and something else, she
Maybe you can come up with this sign
whatever you like, she can give it to you there
completely differently. She can stop her.
some additional data.
That's why these stories with
automation,
ah, well, aishka is the main one there
automation tool, but here
It is important that this module is also
written by a programmer who understands
what it does and how it will work.
Because after such AIs it is necessary
the code is put in, which
normalizes the response that forces
issue the AI ​​in the format that
should be at the exit. That is, Aishka,
Of course, it can be built in
automation,
but it should be between
between the code that checks that
is fed to the input and checks that
Aishka gives out and brings to a state
structured exit.
So, here, probably, it’s also me, in general,
I said about this. And then I'll show you more
using examples.
Communicate, communicate with the human
language, with a system.
No need for extra
some kind of hello, goodbye and
there, sorry, I didn't understand you, our
human speech. It can be difficult,
because when you communicate with Saisha,
Today it is already at such a level that
sometimes you catch yourself just thinking,
that, well, you somehow forget yourself. It's complicated.
Considering that it is now everywhere
are still being implemented,
I don't know, automation robots, probably
It's better not to anger them and continue communicating,
how they communicated, said hello and goodbye.
But overall it's rubbish, of course, yes,
for the system.
Well, here I am too, probably, but in general
said, if you have some kind of long
discussion,
save the result and start new ones
sessions. Don't be afraid to create new ones
sessions. Now I'll show you that too.
Okay, well, let's go, I guess I'll do it now
I'll turn on the demo again and
I'll show you
once again, how the raft is constructed from the inside, what is in
what it is and how it works.
So, a
top panel. Here we are now taking
project,
we are creating a new project
from scratch.
project name. And here you describe aa
instructions, the main instructions, which
will always be in memory. That is this
the instructions will, uh, work inside
each request. That is, uh,
In general, all i-models work.
exclusively with prontas. What you
you give in the text. All the rest are these
Here are the shells that are convenient in the form of an interface,
in the form
there are, I don't know, some pictures. All,
what will you be forging, some
additional buttons, and systems,
created specifically there for, I don't know,
the same clddesign, system for
management
design, design systems, how they
are called,
brand books and so on. Inside it's all the same
there is always text. That's when you're here
creating a new project, you are here
you describe there
general title.
Well, so be it.
it will be like this.
We are creating a project, and inside
which, that is, this folder, everything that you
you will do within this project,
will use the information,
which you have on the right
window. Here the instruction is just that,
what I just wrote. You can in
come and fix it at any time. A
There is a scheduled work schedule here when
you have some kind of automation. And in
We won't touch on this further today.
we will, but when will you have any
agents in the system, you can contact these agents
talk, set a schedule according to which
they will work. For example, each
Go check my mail in the morning and let's go
Give me a summary. This is exactly what is being done
Here. And then either go read it, I don’t
I know the news from such Telegram channels and
again there and prepare for me
some summary information.
It's all managed here. Context -
This is the same folder that you have.
on the computer, which will be used later
the documents that you will be putting together
add to chat. For example, you want to
to ask something, you add here. I
I made it for myself, but it has some demo data.
I'll throw it in just a second.
It doesn't matter, let it be
A
you upload data here, this data
will be saved in your working folder.
There is also a memory folder. This is a constant
project memory. I'll go to mine now.
working project, so that it is more visual
show because I already have it here
a lot of information.
There are four types of memory. Memory of
user. And this is what Claude is holding.
always in my head. Who am I, what am I about,
What am I talking about, what is the purpose of my work in
this project and so on. That is it
information about me, how to approach me
treat me like that
interact.
There is, uh, a memory called
reference. And this
links to some external sources and
some external data and examples. That
I have one here, for example,
reference map site map.
I once told him that my main
The site is Range, go to it, collect
from there, everything that you consider necessary. Well,
I mean, not everything that you think is necessary,
there, take the structure from there so that you
understood what products I was working with.
And all this is stored here in a permanent manner.
memory. Next time I come
and I say: “I’m told from the website: “Get it
such and such information or check, I have
On the website there is this, that, or me
made some changes, for example, in
my product and I say: "You check it out,
What is written on the website about me? I
I found a mistake there, but I don't need him
say what kind of site it is, in what section
climb the site. He's coming here, he's coming.
pulls out of this, from this memory
information about my site and it goes and
takes away." Information project. And here
general information, again, there you have it
I have a brand system here, yes, like
build for me there, how to design
documents. There are some here. What's there?
There are more, I don’t remember myself anymore.
So, here, uh, well, there are big blocks of,
What should they be called? Probably a project inside.
project, yes, a project within the company. Here
They are described here. With this memory
the work is carried out in exactly the same way in this
window. That is all we have today
we say it
as simple as a calculator
here, uh, is the only thing you need
what will be done is to start a project for yourself,
start working with it. Next to you is this one
Aishka will figure it out herself and will tell you herself,
where to go and what to do. You don't need to
climb through these files. You don't need them.
even remember where they are. Here I am
Here is the folder now, I opened it for you
I'm showing it. I didn't open it myself.
once.
Aa
you are inside the dialogue when you need to
to emphasize something
attention, for example, remember me there
Today they don't call him Sasha there, but
Masha, I don’t know, there’s something else there. I have
the project is not like that. I have a website
moved there, there. You tell him
say: "Just remember these now
data, he remembers them himself and in
will use them in the future
from here." And there is also a fourth type
memory, it's called feedback. This
your reaction to his answers. For example,
when I showed you the technical specifications for MiniP,
I had a numbering there, and when I told him I
I gave him a promt, he said something to me
wrote and started asking questions. Here he is
I wrote 50 questions there, then we
We continue to communicate with him, and I continue to communicate with him
the numbering continues. This is the one
the most feedback I gave him because
which is earlier if they start with him
to work, it starts on each block
write some numbers, and sometimes there
there's also point 1a, there's point 10b, and
you sit, racking your brains and instead,
just to answer him quickly, yes,
you read there the first one is this and that, the second one
this one, that one and the third one agree,
the fourth one there, I don't know, update
data, extract it from some website,
It just speeds up the work. Right here
It's in these feedbacks that he remembers this
the format that is more convenient for you to work with.
We always prepare documents for me in the following format
RKDO, because they are good there
are being eaten. Keep links at all times
in such and such a format, use it here
this and that, that and that. This is permanent memory
project
about how to work. And the folder
contextual is what we work with.
So. And returning to the sessions, that is
Here I have a project, open Rains.
When I need to launch something new
work, I open
eh, here's this window. Now I'm cooking there,
I don't know, peach a-
there for the investor,
For example. I'm doing it for the first time now. I
I go into this window and feed it there
additional data. If
I mean I don't have them here
inside this folder or they are not connected
I have it somewhere on external storage, I
I describe the task to him here. I have
a session like this appears, a frame
which I work. Here I have it
You can hang them with just a pin
the conveniences there are those sessions with which I
Working. Here it is. Lyudmila
Bulavkina, hello. A
I smiled. Yes. Yes, yes.
Here. AND
a new session is started. As part of this
During the session I only talk about the topic
which I need now. I'm cooking
investment presentation. I communicate here
just about this. If it dawned on me there
is this moment something new or do I need
switch to another task, I start
new session. So, ae, as if
the memory is shared by design, it's located
Here. Files are always accessible from anywhere
sessions, but in the context window what
we are working now, it is located here
within the framework of such small sessions. Like this
this way, I always get quality,
net result, ae, in which there is no transition
I don't jump from topic to topic, right?
Now I was talking about investments, but
Now let's report there with competitors.
Oh, but there's some cool competitor there,
He probably has great marketing.
Let's see what he has, how they are
do this marketing.
If you do all this within one window,
Okay, we'll get porridge. We have in
there will be an investment presentation and
competitors, and about marketing, and more about
something, and there about planning
traveling somewhere. A
in general, in this part, probably,
All. There can be any projects
quantity, you start them. Uh, the most
simple thing you can do right there
as a result of today's meeting,
go create a project, identify yourself and
start communicating with the fetus on the topic: "And how
"Should I work with you now?"
Let's continue.
So, projects.
Oh, I probably said that too.
in general.
tools and connectors.
This is probably the next stage.
will be the one you start with
interact. E you will come to him
yourself, and you will set it up
on one's own. I'll show you now, simply,
how easy it is to do. AND
no need to try now
there you need to remember what tools there are.
In the process of your work you will understand
your data is stored there. How about me?
connect this tool? Let's start with
product, which is called Obsidian.
This
a thing that will lie on your
computer as long as you work
within the framework
with the project, within the framework of his work as
would be a contour, within the framework of its window and with
your files that you store
myself. At that moment when you gradually
you'll crawl over,
someone will crawl over, someone needs it,
Some people don't need it, for corporate purposes
storage, for example, on Wikipedia, on another
something, obsidian on your local
computer, you will no longer need it. A
What is obsidian?
And, actually, this obsidian
popularized by Andrei Karpati, founder
Openя. He suggested using it as
one of the main tools, therefore
How can you trust this guy?
And in your project folder somewhere
At this point there will be a ton of files.
A, a and
each new session he doesn't know what
your files are there. When you tell him
give a request and refer to what is here
you have it there,
eh, he will do the following. He will take it
this folder, I'll go and comb through the whole thing. ate
I've combed through all the tokens and found everything you have.
You've run out of tokens and can't use them anymore.
work, wait for it to pass
timeout, and you can continue running.
Obsidian is such a local, uh, base
data, and, the source of data, in which
are your files.
This is probably where it needs to be shown.
It looks like this
right now, just a second.
This is what it looks like.
You've probably seen a lot of these too.
pictures. I just pressed the magic button here
button. Now I have this base as it were
she's going to, but, uh, let her go get ready.
Here, besides the beautiful animation, she is neither
What is this animation for?
Means,
each of these dots is some kind of, like
install it now so that it is Each
the dot is some kind of file. And I have
there is, ah, well here it is, actually, that's all
project base for the RS company. Here
here, each dot is separate
file, there are investments,
Range products here can fail,
go to some other tabs and
and so on. That is, this is a connection of files.
And this connection, and this whole thing has
another index. And when we connect
obsidian to our project, or rather
say not to the project, but to Claude,
and because all the connections, they
occur at the application level, not at the
project level.
And when we connect it to our
fruit, I don't need to say now that
You have a file there and I don't need it.
speak Yiddish everything. I refer to
that which
use the Obsinan source for that
data enrichment.
He understands the context, he addresses
this obsidian on the inside
connection, goes, takes the index file,
understands that what he needs lies in
such and such files. He
pulls out only what you need, you save
tokens, you save time, you have
a quick answer is instantly received.
What else? And obsidian is like this
maybe it will be enough for someone,
for a long time, someone will quickly outgrow it
and will go to some other ones
corporate systems. Wiki tables. Well,
I showed you the wiki. Let's have the tables
I'll also show you how to do one of the simple ones
tools and how to work with it and
I'll show you how this whole thing is connected.
table.
For example, I have one like this one
database. It's called NOCA. We
we can now
So.
But it was wrong.
This is just an example. I also link everything
I'll send it. AdB is a corporate database
data. She is cloudy. You can just
take a subscription and start using it
online. There is a similar one
The base is called Air Table. Also links
I'll give it to myself later.
Exactly the same. The only thing now
They cut off Russia. I'm not sure that
She is now A no, it opened. Ah, well
That's right, VPN, that's why everything opened up.
But I couldn't pay anymore. They
just somehow on some hard, low
payment options were disabled at this level.
These are cloud databases. But here it is,
for example, the same NOCA, it
is installed into the contours of your company.
And we installed it at our place. Here he is with us
is located on the NOCA Rangs domain. And what
is this what it is?
You probably all work with Google.
tables. Super powerful, cool stuff.
Ah, but it's not a database, it's a set
tables. NOKA is like Google on
steroids, in which it is possible to install
relationships between tables, between
fields, and enter your own
some fields, formulas, everything that
whatever you like. That is, it’s right here, you
work in an adjacent format, like
Google. Let me tell you now
I'll show you an example of how to create there
new base.
Create a new table.
Here we have a title:
field, date,
drop-down lists, checkboxes, selects,
multiselects, anything you like.
product.
Oh.
Then you work here in a completely different way
Here is the simple format that everyone is familiar with. A
This
database.
But simple, which can be used
everyone there is a leader or everyone there
an employee at his workplace. This
a simple tool, but it gives huge
opportunities because there is here
These are the magic buttons that
are called MTP server. We're coming in,
Click the add button.
I won't add anything here now. I'll tell you
I'll show you right now how she
in the final form it looks like. I missed it. A
What Wednesday is this? This is where you are now
created? Here
This is Nka. Nok DB. I'll send you the links later.
And this tool allows you to connect,
ah, or rather, this base has the ability
connections to your cloud. Here I am now
I open my cloud's settings. I have
Here are the connectors.
And here I have, for example, 1 2 3che
bases of our internal DB, which was
It's collected right now, well, I'm with you
I made it from three fields there, and we have these
databases, for example, are downloaded there for me
there is a large volume of data from Odiska. I
I built myself on the basis of this system
now a-a
vacancy management. control
покаччи пойздунков.
I can show you the same thing just like that
This is roughly what it looks like.
Let's open it
Hunter.
How was this product created? I
Now, a small digression. How
can be used in daily work
here are tools like, for example,
database and database related
Aishka? I post a vacancy, and I come in
nahhunter, as usual, I'm creating there
vacancy, again, of course, with
with the help of Iaya. And I set it up on Eeyore's side
first, I have a connector that comes from there
I was just pulling out the data. But, as I
he said, if we pull it out now,
eh,
if we now extract data from
the same hunter, at every request I
I will get different results. Here for
in order to always receive the same
The result is that I came and made a sign.
It's super simple and super small.
Job title, link to DT, ID
Job openings, salary, status, description
vacancies, full description, how it works
I'm hanging on Hunter, plus metadata.
The screening schedule is how I will
evaluate a-a
candidate.
This is my data, which is for each
The vacancies, of course, vary.
And the start date of the vacancy, end date and
screening indicator on, screening
turned off.
Having such a base, I connect it to AI.
And now when I tell her: "Go to
Headhunter and upload new data to me and
put them here," she goes on
Headhunter, pulls out the data, and she has
there is no way to make a mistake and post it here,
I don't know, should I write the name there?
vacancies, date field, or something else
or somehow fix this format. She
comes, reads the format, she goes to
dhaunter, pulls out all my stuff from there
vacancies,
saves here. Same with
candidates.
I create aa description as I want
work with candidates. Here I have
they are written there, and I have an assessment from
Aishki, I have a compliance index.
candidate for my screening, which
attached to the job description. Link
on the candidate, there are general positions, and so on
further on, there are some fields. I do them myself
I determine what I need for this and how
I have to work with this.
Now that I, uh, come into my own
code,
I connect these databases here and
I connect it here, a connector to the hunter,
I can tell the fertilized person what to do,
How do I select people, what vacancies are there?
I should publish and so on. He walks,
It does it all on its own.
And this is essentially another product there,
which was created in
in about the same amount of time as
I used to spend time on reviewing candidates and
to work with vacancies. That is, here it is
look at 150 candidates there.
During this time I built a system,
which now walks on its own for me,
collects this data on the hunter,
scares according to my description, according to my
requirements
and gives me this interview, and here
Refuse these immediately.
Alexander, please tell me, are you
I gave the connector access to my personal
xnhunter's office?
And I'm talking about this now, we're before that now
we'll get there,
I'll tell you now.
So, the tables have spoken, Vicky,
we talked, and the databases in general are also mine
showed, uh, how it's all set up.
So, we're getting a little out of line now,
ah, this very timing, therefore
I'll try to speed up a little now.
A,
Come on, come on. So, here's how I am now
I'll answer Albert's question once. A,
connection
Brix24,
connecting the world, who works with it
many. And if someone uses this
with these things raft, yes, for offline
meetings, Zoom, any connection, and
is carried out as follows. I
I don't program anything here. I'm coming
V
raft.
Now I'll try to find where I am
connected.
Let's take a fruit as an example. Here it is
since I have it turned on here.
Does anyone use these? People
They definitely use it.
Bones are used.
A digital voice recorder is a cool thing for
participation in offline meetings, but he has
Absolutely terrible e connector and no
is it possible to download from it at all?
data only through their curve
an application that has no
automation.
Well, there is nothing.
What am I writing to him? Request. Do I need it? Yes.
I want to after the meeting, not open
something and then not explain what I
I met so-and-so there, we
talked about this and that. I write to him:
"Give me a simple solution so I can
unload raw data into transcription from the fruit.
And for the feast - this is what they offer,
the fruit itself offers. Works very well
crooked. A local solution is enough for me
to upload a file to MDT. Search and
Check out what Reddit and
GitHub.
It rustles for 15-20 minutes,
gives me some kind of instructions,
suggestions, something else, says that
I need to go and do it and where can I get it from?
key. And, I repeat, he doesn’t have it.
normal solution.
Claude does not find the solution himself. He says:
"There is a crooked solution on GitHub, but
"It works." Okay. He tells me:
"Where is the key?" I say, "This one
key." He says, "Yeah, like, this one.
It should have been saved not like this, but like this."
Tyn-tyn-tyn. All. Here we are with him
ended the conversation.
My next request.
I'm coming to check. Show me the entries in
fetus. He pulls everything out of the fruit for me,
what i have. I have a connector to
a fetus to which there is no connector.
What's next? I open my Cork
Project,
I come here and write there. Me today
I was talking to this guy
investments. A
The IKlod project knows about my investments,
because I do this, they are lying at
him in memory.
Give an assessment of this conversation, pull it out
from there are important things that I need
take into account in the next presentation,
Fix a commit from him for me and so on
further. That's it, I told him that and left.
study. There I open a new session and
I start working with something. Yes, they have it here.
I have more than one light bulb right now
It's not on fire, but if I do something now
I'll send it, when it's done, it's here
it lights up, it has a yellow light, like
you need feedback, or
blue light, like I'm done, go
look.
I'm going back there in 3 minutes, he,
accordingly, he climbs onto the raft,
pulls out the transcription, that's all
decrypted, supplied by my
investment project and gives me a summary
information.
As for headhunter, headhunter doesn't have
connector to
for some external systems. They have
api, but you will need
write them a letter and explain why
you api, they've been looking at it for a week,
They give the key. I have a vacancy posted on
hunter. I say, "Dude, here I am now,
Sorry, I'm in this format because
This is the format of communication with Claude." I am with Claude
I say, "Dude, I don't have a week to wait,
What will HTHunter answer me? Find me
solution. I'm probably not here now
I'll find this download where I did it.
connection.
I guess I have it, maybe, or, well, or
Here
It doesn't matter. It's done in exactly the same way. I
I come here, well, it's just better there
do it through code, yes, if we work with
programming, with some
automation and so on, it's better
do it through code. I come there and
I say: "Find me a solution to
"See what's on GitHub."
It rustles for about 10 minutes in the same way,
comes back and says: "There is a solution
It's a bit crooked, but it works. It
pretends - e web application oh, it
pretends to be a mobile application.
The only thing you'll need is, uh,
register,
log in to Hunter and in the line
"browser pull out the key." This one
the key is yours, but it's being updated there
about once there, I think, 8 weeks,
or something like that or at 12
weeks. Like, "Okay." I say: "Where
find the key?" There, there. Click
such and such a button. I go in and pull it out
Key, I'm already answering him here in the session:
"Here's the key for you." He comes back and
says: "I connected you, that's it
"It works." Everything is as if I had
connecting the canter. I have a cloud now
he pulls it out himself
the vacancies that I have posted there. A
can we make him publish them?
You can do anything else. Is it necessary?
Okay, who needs it, I don't need it. U
I don't have that kind of turnover there, and I
This is not necessary all the time. But for those who
necessary, he, accordingly, can do it for himself
This is to automate. Exactly the same.
Connecting to Bitrix. We are all working
in Bitrix since the first day of creation
companies. He didn't have a normal
connector to Bitrix. I come into fruition,
I say: “I need Bitrix because
We work with him. Everything is there. A
find a solution. In the same way he goes to
GitHub reads everything for about 10 minutes and then comes back.
back, he says: "There is such and such a key."
But he, the only thing that is
It's not a full-fledged API, but it can do it.
send something. Okay, let's think,
How to do it. Aa
He himself, Claude, finds a solution for me. He
says: "Okay, I have an idea. Look,
Bitrix has it
key. You come in and do one.
key, just write from yourself and give
he has the right to send packets there
requests. And next to them, Bitrix has it
open documentation on the entire APE. I am her
I'll connect it for myself. He connects me
API connector and includes documentation.
He says, "Now that you do this to me,
request, get me all the information there
transactions." It goes into the description
Bitrix API, looks at how the API is structured,
forms a request, sends it there,
returns the answer to me.
At Bitrix at the time when
I connected it, but there was no normal API for it.
in order to work with it. Now at
me, ah,
I am today
I made a request just for demonstration purposes.
how it works. Just a second.
So I made a request.
And how many deals do I have in my funnel?
is there a project? For what amount? Here he is
went. I'm just like this is my request
this one line. Everything else is his
I connected it myself. I didn't tell him which one
use connector. He knows himself
already, working on the project that I have
Btrix CRM and he has this very one
summoner. He found a funnel, he pulled it out
data, he showed me all the numbers. I
I say: "Seberi, I find it beautiful that ilg with
with this data."
I didn't tell him, again, he's in
context, he takes my brand Brandbook,
and here I have a crooked brandb
local machine because now I
I assemble it in Claude Design, and it suits me
In short, he produced a dashboard. I give it to him
remark: "You have a brand name
the company should be unified, not
with a multi-colored inscription, logo."
Okay, he went and found the logo.
And, well, and then I'll add some more to them there.
numbers from another funnel. Ah, well, this one
Here is the request. Here, here is the result. A,
Now, just a second, I opened the result, it
you are not shown.
Here is the result, what he collected for me
his.
He pulled this data out of Bitrix for me
Now
in 5 minutes and made me a dashboard, and, on
in which everything is reflected beautifully.
This is to the question of, a
that's the thing, everything is getting outdated, right?
Why the hell do I need some dashboard inside?
Bitrix or why the hell do I need any other system?
there's also additional control, uh, there,
I don't know about other dashboards that
You need to keep in mind which link
go where you are, see what I'm there
I will see, remember, and then I will open it again,
what if it breaks?
Now I just come to the raft and say:
"Go and build me a dashboard that I
I want to see."
Okay, let me try a little more.
speed up so that, well, questions, questions,
when will it be possible to ask. Alexander,
I will leave time on purpose. Now at
I'm still there, I'll do it quickly now
Click through the slides, be sure to answer questions
I set the time. I'll try for 5-7 minutes
finish, and we'll have half an hour there
question. Haunter is connected, 1C is connected
a little bit differently, but the data that
I need them, they are now downloaded from me
NokB. I have AOCDB connected to this
myself, well, AIL and so on. A, AP MCP
I won't bother my head before then. Ah, well,
MCP is such a universal, more
human shell over apium. And a, and
MCP from Claude connects normally
in human language. Say: "Connect
I need this and that." He will say it himself, he will be able to
he will connect or he won't be able to. If
He'll say he can't, send him away.
somewhere far away and say: "Go and
"Sort it out." He will go and sort it out and
then eventually he will be able to. And that's exactly how it was with
with the fruit, exactly the same thing happened with the hunter.
And if there is a tool at all,
to which you have no connection,
and I probably won't now
switch off so as not to waste time,
uh, the fetus has its own connector to
Google me.
It is installed in exactly the same way and works.
Uh, that's all you can do.
Today on the computer, Claude can do
exactly the same on the computer. If you
you use some services, it, uh,
and he has a connection, then all these
services are available to him. If you work
with some instrument that
there's nothing at all, I don't know, there
an antediluvian site that can't do anything
connect, you, uh, say, so that he
I went and explored this site through
Chrome. He opens it like you would
opened, he enters the search string,
opens the desired website and starts following it
crawl with a mouse. A
a similar tool appeared at
GPT, in this Open, was called One Atlas.
This is a browser. When I saw it, I
The first one that went did it. I just told him
opened access and said: "Go to the site
"Kusvila, order me a shawarma."
He went, put it down, found shawarma, added
add to cart. Uh
the only thing he told me later was
like, how will you pay and where?
deliver. Well, like, if you give him
all this data, then he will do all this
on one's own. So if there is something wrong with that
You can work in Odinskaya through Google
Chrome, just if you have Odiska,
for example, with the web version, then you can
Google Chrome in vain,
I don't know why she would go there.
renamed any positions or
someone else.
Does Claude also have connectors for others?
additional data sources. That
Yes, if your specific needs require it
some bigta, marketing, analytics,
finance, consulting, jurisprudence,
medicine, there's anything there, most often
They have connectors. And if you don't
you know, but you may not know them completely,
You come to the boat and say: "Find
give me a source that I can connect to
to you with such and such data. He is for you
will dump all the most modern databases
data and say: "I can do this one, this one
I can’t, but this is paid.” But
He will connect it all himself.
And we probably won't touch on skills now.
we will. This is a separate big topic. A
if you do any repetitive
tasks or you work with the same ones
data, otherwise you can, uh, then this
Prompt should be packaged into a skill so that it works
always the same. And then you just
line of pronto instead of text, so that there
Don't write the same text over and over again.
and not explain every time what is needed,
just indicate the name using a slash
skill, you give the input data, and he
ran. Okay, let's do this again,
I guess I'm still a small piece
I'll touch this one directly for 3 minutes. What
do we still have any left there? And so,
I'll touch on automation now, agent
until I touch. And, well, that's all, basically,
I have,
So what is automation and what is it?
what to do with this? Well, uh, let's get back to
to my headhunter.
I filled the first vacancy while working
just in Claude's window,
just in the promting mode, yes, I told him
I wrote, he pumped it out for me there and so on
further. And it works, it eats up tokens.
If you also tell him: "Go and pick it up there,
I don't know, there were 50 of them there
resume", he will go and pick them up - eh
a good performer and will eat everything
tokens, and you will sit for half a day without
tokens.
And in order to shorten, well,
speed up this work, do it,
firstly, more automatic, and I,
Actually, Nok has already raised this base
for the following vacancies. And while I'm working,
I continue with her, but now there is a big block.
Eh, now I'll show you how
it works.
Taktaktak.
Is there such a product as M8, and NODA 8 NODA
there or NODA infinite NODA.
This is probably one of the most popular right now.
popular products that
are used in that very wipe coding,
when you can program without knowing how
program when you can
create automation without knowing how
create automation.
I did the following. No, I made a raft.
I made it for him, and he prepared it for me,
accordingly, and those requests that
I need to do it. I have it here,
For example, now there is a synchronization of vacancies.
It looks like this.
Every 6 hours, every day he goes to
HeTr, takes vacancies, takes
job description. Ten-tyn. All of these
Nodes are executed in turn. Here you can
Now
press the button and it will show you exactly how
It all works. Here they are running. But
He just updated my job postings.
NOCDB.
Next aa responses
he's running
and synchronizes new responses, which
appeared. The same thing is worth it here
schedule.
And every 4 hours he checks for responses,
which came to me for a vacancy.
Then it starts, uh, I'll tell you now,
where it is called. Ah, SIM card responses.
Here is a filter right away. That is him
checks according to, ah, my
in my opinion
scoring, description, scoring regulations,
and who is suitable for this vacancy, who is not
fits.
That is, those things that can be on Lita
count and
reject it right away, yes, there's the age,
salary, place of residence is not there
comes up, there is a person from far away, there is another one
something. So he immediately told me
resume of candidates, here it is
It's called prescoring, let's do it now.
let's open it. Here he is
Now. No, it's turned off.
He runs me through the scoring and
indicates, uh, okay, he passed the scoring
according to my requirements, and he is potentially
suitable, but it needs to be done now
Detailed scoring using AI. If
If he definitely doesn't pass, then he marks him
to refusal. And I have the following workflow
it's starting here, mass
refusal.
He checks all those who are rejected. To everyone
writes a personal letter. Not
individual. I wrote before
individual, now writes a typical one for
token savings. Writes a typical and
Stranihunter transfers him to
status, well, refusal status. And those who
suitable, marks, required
additional verification in my opinion
scoring. It's not finished here yet
I didn't need to connect this very thing. AND
the next step, accordingly, is to
Don't eat tokens and how to avoid doing this
There are 50 resumes there at once, I will have it
go there once an hour and pull it out
three resumes each,
process them and give me these
definitely missing the point, but this makes sense
have a conversation. So I'm on
search
Now people have stopped wasting their time there.
That is, those hours for viewing and those
vacancies that had to be filled
Summary: I'm not spending them now. And this
a system that operates at the level
companies. That is, now any employee
there, ah, the head of the department, if
he needs a person, he will be exactly the same
use this thing.
This is another product that
it was created just like that, well, over time
analysis of vacancies. But what else, uh, about this?
should I say? And that's exactly what I'm talking about
I'm finishing.
This automation
It wasn't me who wrote it, of course. Claude has this one
There are connectors here.
And this connector has a connector
kneitemu.
I told him what I needed. I gave it to him
the base that I have,
connected
hunter. He set up access for me before.
to hdhunter. He, accordingly,
I have all the keys and everything else. I told him
said: "Now go and collect all this."
This is what I showed you just now, here it is
I didn't make these pipelines.
He made them.
I just hit the publish button,
and they developed it.
This is something you can do without knowing how
programming in general. That is to say, I don't
I didn't write a single line of code here for that,
to get it all going.
So. And what else? Well, I guess so.
automation.
What's with you?
set tasks and make Claude do it
interrogate you. It was at this moment that
You, uh, value ideas. It was at this very moment
the moment you come up with,
and Claude doesn't do anything, well, any Aishka
doesn't make anyone smarter. She gives
super must by time. You are now what
you can do it yourself
run in a parallel session. And at
My work is structured as follows.
I'm giving some right now, for example,
there, yes, I have a focus on investment there
project. I'm doing this part now and
I collect a lot of data there. I collect
market data, analysis, competitors and
and so on. I give it to him, that is, I get there
up to some stage, I need to go there
add data. I give him the task
separate session go study this. In another
sessions study this and so on. While he
There's some rustling going on there, I'm doing something else. There
I'm finishing writing and looking for new questions.
may arise. He finished writing. And I
I come, I accept, I don’t accept, I clarify,
I take the data and go check it because
he may lie. I'm going to check on those
the sites he links to are there
this information or not, because, a,
I will be responsible for these figures later
investors when I say: "Here
look, this number, I know it, because
that I checked it." And that's how
work is built when I have a lot
sessions, and I just kind of throw it in there
and I get a verified result from there.
If you don't try it, delete it.
trash, leave the important stuff, connect
tools, let's be specific
context. What else? Well, basically,
That's probably all. And I have it here
two more slides. This is just an assessment,
which, uh, Raft showed me after that,
how he did it, yes, this very system,
our management system, its assessment
approximately 2.54 million rubles for implementation. This
about 5 months. and is not included in
the cost of portal administration,
infrastructure and support for development
after release. We've been here for a week now
Saved money is like earned money. We are for
We implemented the MS management system this week.
production for which we would give 5
months and there are 3.5-4 million rubles. Vicky, we are for
a week we implemented a system that
is estimated there at another 4 million rubles. Still there
several months of custom work,
internal, it doesn't matter.
And now I have shown you the system
management of work with HDHunter. Search
vacancies, time saving, ready
tool within the company.
Here,
I guess I'm ready to finish on that note.
and move on to your questions.
Everyone's microphones are turned off. Turn on
or stretch out your hand and we will.
I wanted to thank you and say that
It's done very cool.
It is clear that the attitude is very pedantic. I wanted
to ask such a global question, which
Mine flies too. Why not take it?
and not to make the same Bitrix 24, write
Claude and do not use external
service? It seems like it's on the surface
question and just like that
Absolutely absolutely so. And we, well, with
We work with Bitrix
many years, there 10 years, I don’t know how long.
As part of this current project, I am with
We all work with Bitrix as soon as possible
a project appeared and they connected us right away
corporate Bitrix. We have everything there
tasks. We have production there, we have
there is the Central Research and Development Center. And now, when production
we brought it into our corporate system,
and on the country of Bitrix we still have
production tasks. Undoubtedly,
the next step will be why the hell should we climb
there, if we are just on our own part
Let's raise the management of these tasks. U
We will still have the CRM chat and tasks there
other. But it's a matter of time,
Of course, he is becoming unneeded for us now
necessary. We have, uh, very fast
the entire infrastructure flows into ours
own self-written system, but
self-written at a very high, constant
level. I have my partner, he is 20
He has been involved in programming for years,
built very complex loaded
systems. And in terms of safety, everything
the rest of us in this sense is everything
Wonderful. Well, and this is a single environment, in
which everything works.
It's clear. And how much does a subscription cost for Claude?
based on these tasks, tokens,
which ones are used?
using this entire infrastructure as an example.
And I have a personal subscription,
I work with mine.
I'm crying now for about, probably, about
$200 per month.
There are three subscriptions: $20, $100
and 200. But I can’t seem to get to 200, although
In fact, I spend 200 plus. A,
Well, in general, there is an opportunity there
buy this one for 100 and buy more later
tokens additionally. I still can't seem to get it
I won't switch to it. Roman, my partner,
He's been sitting at 200 for a long time. Ah, start with
twenty.
Uh, in a week you'll be up to 100,
because you will understand that you are missing something.
But I wouldn't jump to 200 right away,
because you will start doing
errors. Errors in work. You will start there
feed the data, it will
It's great to chew because
He has a ton of tokens, he has limits
they don't run out quickly there, but you
You will feed us with unnecessary data. Here
This is the limit when you have
subscription for 100, it makes you
will force you at some point when you
you'll get stubborn, think that you're something
you're doing it wrong. The token must be saved.
It's clear that now you can fill it up
money there. Well, I gave an example, yes, in
Friday, the company that spent 500
million dollars in tokens. Here you go
we probably all have the same
It will be smaller, but better.
It's clear. I'm also thinking of switching to 200.
And one more question. That was very
The management is described very well.
production, candidate management
SHA. Is there a similar project or
the thought of doing the same
structured sales management?
This is so that the club can see every stage
funnels, there, I don’t know, gave
recommendations to the salesperson, made a sari
every call, every meeting and immediately
gave some kind of answer there, I don't know,
to the head of the sales department or there
to the commercial director, who is in
management is, and the owner too
Someone sent a sari every day.
Here. Something in this direction Alexander
did you think or didn't you think? If yes, then maybe
share your experience.
Of course, this is the first thing about us
what do you need to think about? Because we are a business
We build everything to make a profit. A
There are a few more layers here. I did this today
I didn't touch it on purpose. Ah, the first thing we
they did it - it was supplemented by agents of agents,
which we currently have listed in
Nutribitrich as employees. These agents
they go around, check the transactions, check
company contacts and so on, are issued from
their name, write data in chats
salesperson and head of the sales department
in order to highlight the problems
there, well, in general, in terms of essence and
spit out data in
analytics where you can see progress,
it gets worse or it gets better.
This is the first layer, the simplest one. He was
made there, I don't know, several months
back, and it seems to work for us. We
Now we're collecting
a large multi-agent system. We have
will be uh
system that
controls everything. Well, how can it not control?
to everyone who sees and knows everything. This
user support, this is
support for employees internally, response to
any question. Uh, including, what about
us with production? Can we?
shove in an urgent order? Ah, can we?
we're there, I don't know, should I give a discount? A
What are our commercial terms? All
information. But there are more layers here. If
I have it connected now
B3X24, I can definitely come now
and tell him: "Go comb through everything for me
the transactions that I have hanging there now
at such and such a stage, and give me a summary of
there are the last dialogues."
He'll just choke on this volume.
he will pull it out, but he will run out of tokens, and
he won't be able to work. They turn on there
other metrics. Up to some level you
you can work independently, but
then other metrics are included. And these
systems, AI, they are not, of course, not
hold the whole context and shouldn't hold
the whole context. They make a selection. That
there is a level there first
search engine, conditionally, yes, these are vectors
bases and so on. That is, he knows that
pull out, and selects the data that
necessary. This is a more complex system. This
a system that is already working on ours
servers, in our environment, not on
Claude, not on my local. Undoubtedly,
This will all happen in the near future.
It's clear. I also wanted to ask about
safety. He still gives these away
data or they are somewhere local or
there is some kind of line where the outline is
is it ending?
I interact with it as a user,
I receive some of my own product, conditionally
there, I don't know, project management. AND
further he is what we worked on, not
transfers to another, third party,
which makes similar requests. Here
I wanted to understand if there was any
you can set a task so that he does what
we came to some product in
as a result of reflection or action,
so that he doesn't transmit them openly
access nowhere.
A
Is there any way to control this?
This is a complex and debatable question.
Of course, all these systems, they
sharpened. The same Anthropic, he
designed for corporate use.
They are primarily interested in
to ensure that your data does not leak anywhere.
They're coming out on the iPhone now, they have
the estimate there is already under a trillion, yes,
overtook the Open Open
Ah, well, here, probably, the level of trust
the same as yours, uh, I don't know,
there's mail somewhere or something else there,
Yes? You work inside as if it were your own
subscriptions, within your own contour. They can
they can leak, but
there is an opportunity to place bets here
additional tools, and which in
including, for example, you asked,
Why don't we connect sales there?
everything else. We have them somewhere here
We're connecting, yes, we're working on it now.
we work locally, but the tool,
who will be doing the analysis
sales, and there is personal data, there
phones, there's anything you want, yes, we have
in transactions, negotiations and so on, so on,
transcribtion, and there will be
filters that will filter out
information that cannot be transmitted
further.
This is something to think about. Uh, I, well,
I doubt that it's clear now,
You can feed it anything, right? You
You can go and kick it out there now
some data, and it will leak there.
The issue of safety is important. Necessary
cut off, need to install additional ones
checks, mechanical ones need to be installed
checks, because to tell Cloud: "No
give it back," he will say, "Okay, I don't
"I'll give it back."
Well, one more question. Sorry about that,
that I took the palm and that's it
I ask questions. I apologize to the public.
I just have a question like this,
Probably more than one. We have
problems with registration, well, of the project. By
In essence, we sell a similar product. AND
it turns out that it's the same client
starts calling everyone
online stores in Russia in order to
get it cheaper or beat someone else's price
dealer. Here. And I also like this product if it
it's implemented somehow differently because
Bitrix has a number checker.
phone, our dealer enters it there. To me
It's kind of interesting to watch
the very product that allows you to
help protect this project, conditionally
saying, well, this or that product, which
The dealer sells so that another dealer doesn't
interrupted. If I understand this correctly
the product that was being discussed for protection
project.
And this product is described, it is
formulated, it is not there yet, we have it
we will, uh,
Well, to implement in the near future. -e
This is within the framework of the restructuring there.
companies to work with a dealer network.
This product will be inside our
dealer circuit. It's unlikely that he will
separately as a product of some kind
be used. That is, it will be exactly
This is an internal tool.
Well, I get it. That is, if you hear him there orally
patent it, he will have his own
uniqueness, then you will somehow
extend to the outer contour.
Do I understand correctly?
Very unlikely.
Yes. Very unlikely.
It's clear. Fine.
Here's to Claude
I understood that I had a task of approximately
three lives. Now I understand with Claude,
What is the task that I can do for me?
there are 100 lives there, but I'm definitely going to live three
I'll do it now.
It's clear.
Focus on everything.
I'm asking approximately the same question here
To Roman. Uh, and, and then we start
talking in swear words because that's all
time looks at it from the point of view
IT specialist, and I look at it from the point of view of how
would be entrepreneurs. There: "Oh, cool
same idea, well, it's possible, yes, for everyone
"take and go for an hour." And then it begins
like: "And what is the overall scope of work for
Is this worth it?" Yes, the same ones
safety. And when we connect there
It's within us, we have everything for this
There is. In order to do this, SAS
the solution is to build something else nearby
one such company.
It's clear. So, I realized that we are this or
presentation or video we will receive this in
in some form. Right, Alexander?
Well, there will be a recording, but the presentation itself,
Well, I'll throw it off, but on her, like, except
slides, I think.
Well, just the video is enough for me to do that.
I'll discuss with my tops what else
It can be done.
Thanks for your answers. Here. Thank you. Was
Interesting.
So, are there any questions in the chat?
If you have any other questions, please ask.
Lyuda about the interface passed. Well, I'll send it.
link. This is Nн Antyn
plots. OK. A
The optimizer solution is ready. What is this?
optimizer solution?
This is an egg service that
automates, manages the funnel already
big one which
and attracted rounds, and earns. Yes.
VPN cloud blocking. How do you fight? A
just like everyone else. I have a VPN with
which I've been working on for the last time, probably
a couple of months. If it's not an advertisement, I can
just name it. This is BOV VPN. Works.
Phew-phew-phew. So far so good. I don't like him at all
I'm turning it off. He works for me
uh, on the iPhone and on the MacBook, it's just constantly
24x7. I stopped doing this in
bell-shaped off Everything works with him.
Fine. Uh, claude blocking, yeah,
They say that they block it very strongly.
We haven't been blocked yet. And I
The main thing is registration through Google
account, and preferably not in the rudomenee. AND
foreign card.
Please also indicate all payment details.
by country of registration. For now, we have, as it were,
It works, but no one is immune.
It may stop tomorrow, but we'll find it.
some other instrument. In terms of
not a tool, but a workaround. Tools
Not yet.
Can I ask Nick Alexander about this?
a service that optimizes the funnel with
attracted rounds, on it
listen, test, watch
compress it somewhere in the chat, if not
it's difficult. Interesting, I just did this
involved. The biggest trick.
Well, we'll ask Lyuda, she'll send it
I can post the link later in the channel
hang.
I'll send it.
Yes.
Thank you,
Alexander, thank you very much for
presentation. It's really cool that
shared real cases of his
business. And in the first part you talked about
that there, using and very important
Right
make a request. Do you use it?
some kind of industrial generators?
If yes, which ones? If not, why not?
No. But
I don't think there's anything wrong with that now
no need. And this one is like
the thing was spinning,
It was probably popularized there at the dawn of time.
the same GPT and everything else. A
The protgenerator is not needed for ordinary ones
requests. Protgenerators are used,
and, for example, in such instruments as
image generator, video generator, and
when you need to assemble a complex promt,
consisting of a large number
identical or exactly described
elements, yes, if when, for example,
it's being done, uh, I don't know, avatar
some, and you need to support
all the time his appearance is the same,
there, well, facial features, you use them
promtgenerator for that, that
collect and promts from the required blocks.
But in this kind of work, well there
in human language it simply writes that
need to.
Well, that means the answer will be the same, right?
What if through the industrial generator, what if you
You can just write it in human language there
in such?
I didn't really use it and I didn't even
looked towards the industrial generators. But I
I don't really understand what you're going to write for
so that the promt would give you away, something
generated, you will owe him
submit a request.
Well, yes,
Well, ask it to Cloud right away, he'll tell you
will tell you how to compose a promt.
Okay, good, thank you.
That's it, no more questions.
I took advantage of the advertisement. Wait a minute
I wrote advertisements.
OK.
Links, Sasha, links,
I'll send you the links now.
Thanks a lot.
Well, I'll hang it on the channel. Everything except the virus.
Well, you can't use a VPN.
no, no,
kmeru, right? And that's it, that's it, except for the virna. I
I'll send you the links,
Yes. I'm also interested in the video.
Well, go ahead and drag it out of the chat,
while it's hanging.
Thank you.
That's it, thank you for your attention. Then we're on
This concludes our discussion.
Thank you, Sasha.
Thank you. Bye.